Yokoya
Katsuda's Sauce
Half a cabbage, potatoes, onions, and...
carrots.
Ms. Maid! You having curry today?
Oh, yes, I believe so.
That's good.
Here. One more on the house.
Um...
Uh, um...
How may I help you?
Um, I've been watching you
this whole time, and...
I was thinking how wonderful you are, and...
I want to be just like you!
I'm honored to hear that.
And... Where can I buy those
clothes you're wearing?
These clothes?
Uh-huh!
I wanted to ask you when I got a chance!
They're the kind of clothes
people don't normally wear, so...
I was thinking I could be
just like you if I wore them!
Oh, Ms. Yuki!
Master Hitoyoshi...
What a coincidence!
I was just at the bookstore, and...
Is it not normal to wear a maid outfit?
Episode 7: You've Finally Figured It Out.
And so, we made plans for next Sunday
to go clothes shopping with Ms. Yuki.
Ogiso Station
Big Brother!
Over here, over here!
Lucky Day
Uh, were we expecting company?!
When I got your message,
I just had to come, too!
You know Ms. Yuki's
rather limited wardrobe?
I want to find out what else looks
good on her, so I'm going to go
with her to buy clothes.
I'm free on Sunday!
No, I understand why you're here, but...
Why are you here?
When I overheard you talking,
I just had to come, too!
That makes no sense, and it's creepy!
My apologies. I thought I had disposed
of all the listening devices.
Well, too bad for you!
There's still one left in the living room!
Could you guys stop engaging in
high-tech espionage behind my back?
I don't trust you to pick out
girls' clothes all on your own.
If you ask me, the trustworthiness
of this team has only gone down.
Um... Excuse me,
pretty and cool-looking lady...
Are you an assassin, too?
Hee-hee!
That's right!
Please don't get involved with Riko, too!
Wow... A mature lady smells so nice...
You're just like Hitoyoshi—
amusing and adorable.
Okay, well, leaving those two aside for now...
Let's pick out some clothes
for you right away, Ms. Yuki!
On Sale Now
Oh! About that!
There's a store I recommend nearby!
A Miss Riko recommendation...
Oh, then let's try there.
Yeah!
Are you ready?!
Yes.
Um, that's...
going to make her stand out
even more than before!
Oh, sorry!
I couldn't resist...
Personally, this one seems more restricting
than the last, which is a problem for me.
She's choosing based on efficiency...
But you look so, so good in it!
It's so cute! I love it!
Hey!
Don't forget! We're here to buy Ms. Yuki
normal clothes that look nice on her!
I know!
Then it's my turn next.
I'll teach you how to coordinate
an outfit like an adult.
What do you think, Master Hitoyoshi?
There'd be all kinds of problems
if you wore that around town!
Indeed...
It would be very hard
to hide my knives in this.
The knives are part of the criteria, too, huh?
Putting that outfit aside, if you're not
going to assassinate anyone anymore,
Wow! Amazing!
do you really need to think about knives?
It's not that. I just feel at ease having
them with me, even if they're hidden.
You're not supposed to carry
hidden knives either, but...
Hey, you two. If you're not
going to take this seriously,
could you just leave us to it?
B1
B2
Rooftop
Theater (Screen 4-8)
Theater (Reception, Shop, Screen 1-3)
Restaurant Town (Restaurant & Café, Event Hall)
Women's Fashion (Youth Fashion, Jeans,
Formal Wear, Fur & Leather, Accessories)
Men's Fashion (Suits & Jackets, Formal Wear,
Casual Wear, Neckties, Dress Shirts,
Leather, Bags)
Cosmetics, Fragrances, Misc. Goods
(Lifestyle Misc. Goods, Makeup,
Skin Care & Body Care, Aroma), Information Desk
Groceries, Perishable Foods,
Side Dishes & Bentos, Bread
Parking Lot
My bad, my bad!
L-Let's go to a normal store next.
Yep... It's pissing me off
that you look great in everything.
You're like a model...
What're you playing at,
sneaking that swimsuit in between?
So, what kinda clothes
do you prefer, Hitoyoshi?
What, me?!
I-I think something like...
a white sundress...
would look nice on her...
Ah, yes, indeed. Indeed, at that.
Man, I am so done with you!
We finished making our choices, but...
It's more like we dodged having to choose
by just buying everything you tried on.
It was too difficult to decide between them.
Hey! They're having a Halloween fair!
I heard Halloween is one of the biggest events
in Japan, but this is really something!
This is awesome! There are so many costumes!
All right! Let's choose Big Brother's
costume for this year right now!
What, we're really doing it again this year?
Of course! Mom looks forward
to it every year, too!
Hey! Wait, Riko!
Trick or treatment!
Don't you mean "treat"?
Ms. Servant was actually a witch!
If you don't gimme candy,
you're goin' straight in the slammer!
Man, this has nothing to do
with Halloween anymore.
Woo-hoo! Sexy!
Miss Riko certainly looks
like she's having fun.
She gets kinda pumped up for it every year.
Horror Movie Festival!
BATTING DEAD 1
BATTING DEAD 2
Terror! King Crab Man's
Experiments
Oh, hey!
They're showing the
Batting Dead zombie movies!
When the world's bases are loaded with the undead,
the fate of humanity depends on one man's batting skills...
That's one of my favorite series!
Oh, sounds like fun! Let's go watch it!
Let's go! Let's go!
Is that okay with you?
That means going to the movie theater, right?
Oh? You're not much of a moviegoer, then?
Do you prefer to watch at home instead?
Not exactly, but movie theaters were mostly...
places I went to assassinate targets
rather than watch movies.
I never saw much of the movies themselves.
R-Right, movie theaters are dark,
not to mention loud, huh?
I've had enough! I'm outta here!
Wait! Don't go that way!
Give me brains!
Don't get any closer! Stay away!
Brains!
Eek!
Zombies... are scary...
What about zombies scares you?
I feel like you'd take them down
in a flash, Ms. Yuki.
W-Well, let's see...
Firstly, I can't stand the
stench of decaying corpses.
Right off the bat, a non-normal answer.
Plus, they're already dead,
so I can't kill them...
Oh, yeah. That's a good point.
To Ms. Yuki, her past is...
What happened in her past
used to be normal life for her.
She just wants to be normal,
but that's all she has.
Furthermore, I have no
experience being a corpse, so...
None of us do! It's fine!
You're an assassin,
and you're afraid of zombies?
You sure are weird!
Look, look, Big Brother!
It's whipped cream heaven!
More like, check out how big that thing is!
Sure you won't spoil your dinner?
I can eat this with room to spare!
Delish!
Do you want some, too, Ms. Yuki?
Oh, may I?
Of course!
How is it?
It's delicious.
Open wide!
Nope, nope, nope!
Not on your life!
Then it's my turn!
Okay, here you go, Big Brother!
H-Hey!
Right? Isn't it good?!
Well, yeah, it is, but...
You're losing your edge, Naka!
You're not living up to the expectations
of someone from the Hikage bloodline.
Be aware of your surroundings at all times.
Never let your guard down.
My apologies, Big Brother Tatsu.
Train your lower body at tonight's practice.
Yes. I'm honored to have your guidance.
Going shopping was so much fun!
Let's go again sometime, Ms. Yuki!
Right!
You, too, Ms. Grace!
If you're going, sure!
Next time, we'll leave Big Brother
behind and have a girls' day out!
Well, that works better for me, too.
See you again, Ms. Grace!
Later!
I'm going to walk Riko back.
What do you want to do, Ms. Yuki?
In that case, I will head home
and begin preparations for dinner.
All right. I'll see you later.
See ya!
Yokoya
You want me to play with you?
There's slobber all over this.
We were out all day today, so...
I didn't get to do the laundry.
Even if Master Hitoyoshi is not here...
I can at least do laundry!
Agemochitaro, let's wash
that toy and towel as well.
Come, now!
Ah! Agemochitaro!
Thunder and lightning?
I wonder if Ms. Yuki is okay.
The power went out...
Was that sound Agemochitaro?
And then...
You got startled and accidentally
sliced Mochita's towel to pieces, huh?
My sincerest apologies.
Don't cry, Mochita!
I will repair your shedding towel later.
Oh, man. I don't know if you're going to
be able to fix something that's this torn up.
I will fix it... with everything I have!
Oh, all right. Then I'll leave it to you.
Isn't that great, Mochita?
Oh, speaking of which,
you're wearing the maid outfit?
Is it because... you didn't really
like the clothes we bought?
It's not that.
I was truly happy about the clothes
we selected and bought together.
It's just that...
I'll be having you attend to me
from today onward.
That is a present from me.
This maid outfit is also a very important
gift, given to me by my master.
It's the only link to him
I still have after his passing.
If you ever decide you want to stop killing,
that's fine by me, Xue.
Back then, I didn't understand
the meaning behind those words,
and I ended up serving him as an assassin.
But now... This maid outfit has given me
the opportunity to be here.
Even if this form of clothing is not
considered to be "normal"...
I want to keep wearing this maid outfit.
Is it odd to think this way?
I don't think it's weird.
Still...
She said it was weird that I'm afraid
of zombies even though I'm an assassin.
Oh, right, Ms. Grace did say
something like that, didn't she?
That's not weird at all, either.
It's not weird to wear the things
you love when you want to,
or to be afraid of things that frighten you.
It just so happened that for you,
it's maid outfits that you like,
and zombies that frighten you, right?
More so, it's normal to have
things we like and don't like,
and it's also normal to want
to cherish those feelings.
So, I think you should just aim for the
norm that works for you, Ms. Yuki.
A norm that works for me...
Yep, yep!
You gotta wait a little longer, Mochita.
We have to make dinner first.
What, you can't wait?
Oh? This towel.
It's the one that was with you
when we took you in.
Maybe it has the scent of his
parents on it or something.
Agemochitaro's... family's...
Um, Master Hitoyoshi.
Hm?
Would it be all right if I tried my hand
at repairing the towel before dinner?
Oh, yeah, it's fine by me, but...
I understand Agemochitaro's feelings, as well.
This bell is the only thing that links me
to my long-lost younger sister.
Oh, your long-lost younger sister, huh?
The mere thought of losing it...
Younger sister...
Wait! Ms. Yuki, you have a younger sister?!